import questionImage from "../assets/question-bucket-1.svg";
export const questions = {
    bucket_name: "Promoting sustainability",
    image: questionImage,
    questions: [{
        question: "In 2015, world leaders got together to adopt the Paris Agreement. What was the Paris Agreement about?",
        options: ["World peace", "Climate change", "International trade", "French cuisine"],
        answer: "Climate change",
        followup_text: "The Paris Agreement was meant to limit the increase in global temperature to 1.5Â°C.",
        source: "https://www.un.org/en/climatechange/paris-agreement"
    },
    {
        question: "What do the terms, Paris Agreement, Kyoto Protocol and Durban Platform, have in common?",
        options: ["They are names of Mission Impossible movies", "They are historical events in the last century", "They are climate change actions agreed by the United Nations"],
        answer: "They are climate change actions agreed by the United Nations",
        followup_text: "The Paris Agreement, Kyoto Protocol and Durban Platforms are outcomes of the UN Climate Change Conference since 1995.",
        source: "https://unfccc.int/process/the-convention/history-of-the-convention#Climate-Change-in-context"
    },
    {
        question: "True or false: Recycling one aluminum can save enough energy to run a TV for three hours.",
        options: ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
        answer: "TRUE",
        followup_text: "Recycling one aluminum can saves enough energy to run a TV for three hours.",
        source: "https://www.mga.edu/sustainability/docs/Recycling_Facts.pdf"
    },
    {
        question: "True or false: Recycling one ton of paper can save 17 trees.",
        options: ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
        answer: "TRUE",
        followup_text: "Each ton of recycled paper can save 17 trees.",
        source: "https://portal.ct.gov/DEEP/Reduce-Reuse-Recycle/Municipal-Recycling-Resource-Center/As-A-Matter-of-Fact#:~:text=Each%20ton%20of%20recycled%20paper,60%20pounds%20less%20air%20pollution!"
    },
    {
    
        question: "Bamboo is hailed as a eco-friendly construction material because...",
        options: ["It grows much faster than timber", "It costs less to harvest and transport bamboo", "It absorbs 40% more carbon dioxide compared to trees" , "All of the above"],
        answer: "All of the above",
        followup_text: "Bamboo is being considered as a replacement for timber in construction, due to its sustainable properties.",
        source: "https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S2214785321001681"
    },
    {
        question: "True or false: It takes more energy to make 1 kg of paper than it takes to make 1 kg of steel.",
        options: ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
        answer: "TRUE",
        followup_text: "Producing 1 kg of paper from timber takes more energy than making 1 kg of steel from iron.",
        source: "https://www.lowtechmagazine.com/what-is-the-embodied-energy-of-materials.html"
    },
    {
        question: "True or false: A website with 100,000 pageviews a month emits 2,112kg of carbon dioxide a year.",
        options: ["TRUE", "FALSE"],
        answer: "TRUE",
        followup_text: "A website with 100,000 pageviews a month emits 2,112 kg of carbon dioxide a year.",
        source: "https://thesustainableagency.com/blog/sustainability-facts-and-statistics-for-business-owners/"
    },
    {
        question: "How many times can paper be recycled?",
        options: ["Up to 27 times", "Up to 15 times", "Up to 7 times", "Up to 3 times"],
        answer: "Up to 7 times",
        followup_text: "Paper can be recycled up to 7 times.",
        source: "https://www.nytimes.com/2010/12/21/science/21qna.html"
    },
    {
        question: "What does GHG stand for?",
        options: ["Ghost hair girl", "Greenhouse gas", "Good and honest games"],
        answer: "Greenhouse gas",
        followup_text: "GHG stands for greenhouse gas, which are gases in the atmosphere that trap heat.",
        source: "https://www.epa.gov/ghgemissions"
    },
    {
        question: "What is a carbon sink?",
        options: ["A wash basin made from carbon fibre", "Something that absorbs more carbon than it releases"],
        answer: "Something that absorbs more carbon than it releases",
        followup_text: "A carbon sink is anything that absorbs more carbon from the atmosphere than it releases, such as plants, the ocean and soil.",
        source: "https://www.clientearth.org/latest/latest-updates/stories/what-is-a-carbon-sink/"
    }
    ]
}
